<specification xmlns="http://jboss.com/products/weld/tck/audit"
               xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://jboss.com/products/weld/tck/audit"
               name="Jakarta Interceptors Specification" id="interceptors" version="2.0" generateSectionIds="true">

    <section id="overview" title="Overview" level="1">
    </section>

    <section id="int_programming_contract" title="Interceptor Programming Contract" level="1">
    </section>

    <section id="terminology" title="Terminology" level="2">
    </section>

    <!-- 2.2 -->
    <section id="def_of_interceptor_classes_and_interceptor_methods" title="Definition of Interceptor Classes and Interceptor Methods" level="2">

        <group>
            <text>An interceptor method may be declared in the target class, in an interceptor class associated with the target class, or in a superclass of the
                target class or interceptor class.
            </text>
            <assertion id="aa">
                <text>Interceptor method may be defined on an interceptor class associated with the target class.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="ab">
                <text>Interceptor method may be defined in the target class.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="ac">
                <text>Interceptor method may be defined in a super class of the target class.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="ad">
                <text>Interceptor method may be defined in a super class of the interceptor class.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>Any number of interceptor classes may be associated with a target class.</text>
            <note>It's not possible to test all the combinations, we only test few basic scenarios.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c" testable="false">
            <text>An interceptor class must not be |abstract| and must have a |public| no-arg constructor.</text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-22</note>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>This specification defines the interceptor method types listed below. Extension specifications may define additional interceptor method
                types.
            </text>
            <assertion id="ca" testable="false">
                <text>Around-invoke interceptor methods (annotated with the |jakarta.interceptor.AroundInvoke| annotation). Around-invoke interceptor methods
                    interpose on the invocation of business methods.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="cb" testable="false">
                <text>Around-timeout interceptor methods (annotated with the |jakarta.interceptor.AroundTimeout| annotation). Around-timeout interceptor methods
                    interpose on the invocation of timeout methods, in response to timer events.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="cc" testable="false">
                <text>Post-construct interceptor methods (annotated with the |jakarta.annotation.PostConstruct| annotation). Post-construct interceptor methods
                    are invoked after dependency injection has been completed on the target instance.
                </text>
                <note>Tested in "Interceptor Methods for Lifecycle Event Callbacks" section.</note>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="cd" testable="false">
                <text>
                    Pre-destroy interceptor methods (annotated with the |jakarta.annotation.PreDestroy| annotation). Pre-destroy interceptor methods are invoked
                    before the target instance and all interceptor instances associated with it are destroyed by the container.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="ce" testable="false">
                <text>
                    Around-construct interceptor methods (annotated with the |jakarta.interceptor.AroundConstruct| annotation). Around-construct interceptor
                    methods
                    interpose on the invocation of the constructor of the target instance.
                </text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="d">
            <text>
                Up to one interceptor method of each interceptor method type may be defined in the same class. More specifically, up to one around-invoke
                interceptor method, one around-timeout interceptor method, and one lifecycle callback interceptor method for each of the different lifecycle
                events may be defined in the same class. Only the interceptor methods of the interceptor class that are relevant for the given invocation
                context are invoked. For example, when a business method is invoked, around-invoke interceptor methods are invoked, but any
                around-construct, around-timeout, post-construct, or pre-destroy methods are ignored.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="f" testable="false">
            <text>Interceptor methods and interceptor classes may be defined for a class by means of metadata annotations or, optionally, by means of a
                deployment descriptor.
            </text>
            <note>Tested in several other sections</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="g" testable="false">
            <text>Interceptors classes may be associated with the target class using either interceptor binding or the |Interceptors| annotation. Typically only
                one interceptor association type is used for any component.
            </text>
            <note>Tested in sections 3.3 and 4</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="h" testable="false">
            <text>An extension specification may use a deployment descriptor to specify the invocation order of interceptors or to override the order specified
                in metadata annotations. A deployment descriptor can be optionally used to define default interceptors or to associate interceptors with the
                target class. For example, the EJB specification requires support for the ejb-jar.xml deployment descriptor and the CDI specification requires
                supports for the beans.xml deployment descriptor.
            </text>
            <note>The ejb-jar.xml deployment descriptor is tested within the EJB TCK. The beans.xml deployment descriptor is tested within the CDI TCK, section
                9.4 Interceptor enablement and ordering.
            </note>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <!-- 2.3 -->
    <section id="interceptor_lifecycle" title="Interceptor Life Cycle" level="2">

        <assertion id="a" testable="false">
            <text>The lifecycle of an interceptor instance is the same as that of the target class instance with which it is associated.</text>
            <note>Tested within 2.2 ba) and 2.2 bb).</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="ba">
            <text>Except as noted below, when the target instance is created, a corresponding interceptor instance is created for each associated interceptor
                class.
            </text>
        </assertion>
        <assertion id="bb" testable="false">
            <text>These interceptor instances are destroyed if the target instance fails to be created or when it is removed.</text>
            <note>Unable to test whether an instance is really destroyed.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c" teastable="false">
            <text>An interceptor instance may be the target of dependency injection. Dependency injection is performed when the interceptor instance is created,
                using the naming context of the associated target class.
            </text>
            <note>Tested within 2.2.1 a).</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="ca">
            <text>With the exception of around-construct lifecycle callback interceptor methods, no interceptor methods are invoked until after dependency
                injection has been completed on both the interceptor instances an the target instance.
            </text>
            <note>Implied by 2.3 ba) and 2.3 c).</note>
            <note>If the PostConstruct callback is defined on the interceptor class, it is not invoked when the interceptor instance itself is created.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="cb" testable="false">
            <text>Post-construct interceptor methods for the target instance are invoked after dependency injection has
                been completed on the target instance.
            </text>
            <note>Tested in 2.3 e).</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="cc" testable="false">
            <text>
                Pre-destroy interceptor methods are invoked before the target instance and all interceptor instances
                associated with it are destroyed.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>The following rules apply specifically to around-construct lifecycle callback interceptor methods:</text>
            <assertion id="da">
                <text>|Around-construct| lifecycle callback interceptor methods are invoked after dependency injection has been completed on the instances of
                    all interceptor classes associated with the target class.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="daz" testable="false">
                <text>Injection of the target component into interceptor instances that are invoked during the |AroundConstruct| lifecycle callback is not
                    supported.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="db">
                <text>The target instance is created after the last interceptor method in the around-construct interceptor chain invokes the
                    |InvocationContext.proceed| method. If the constructor for the target instance supports injection, such constructor injection is performed.
                    If the |InvocationContext.proceed| method is not invoked by an interceptor method, the target instance will not be created.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="dc">
                <text>The |AroundConstruct| interceptor method can access the constructed instance using the |InvocationContext.getTarget| method after the
                    |InvocationContext.proceed| completes.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="dd" testable="false">
                <text>Dependency injection on the target instance is not completed until after invocation of all interceptor methods in the |AroundConstruct|
                    interceptor chain complete successfully. Around-construct lifecycle callback interceptor methods should therefore exercise caution when
                    invoking methods of the target instance since dependency injection on the target instance will not have been completed.
                </text>
                <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-26</note>
            </assertion>
        </group>
    </section>

    <!-- 2.3.1 -->
    <section id="interceptor_environment" title="Interceptor Environment" level="3">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>An interceptor class shares the enterprise naming context of its associated target class. Annotations and/or XML deployment descriptor
                elements for dependency injection or for direct JNDI lookup refer to this shared naming context.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>Around-invoke and around-timeout interceptor methods run in the same Java thread as the associated target method.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="ba">
            <text>Around-construct interceptor methods run in the same Java thread as the target constructor.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>It is possible to carry state across multiple interceptor method invocations for a single method invocation or lifecycle callback event in the
                context data of the |InvocationContext| object. The |InvocationContext| object also provides information that enables interceptor methods to
                control the behavior of the interceptor invocation chain, including whether the next method in the chain is invoked and the values of its
                parameters and result.
            </text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <!-- 2.4 -->
    <section id="invocationcontext" title="InvocationContext" level="2">

        <assertion id="a" testable="false">
            <text>The InvocationContext object provides information that enables interceptor methods to control the behavior of the invocation chain.</text>
            <note>Statement of intent</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="ba">
            <text>The same |InvocationContext| instance is passed to each interceptor method for a given target class method or lifecycle event
                interception. This allows an interceptor to save information in the context data property of the InvocationContext that can be subsequently
                retrieved in other interceptors as a means to pass contextual data between interceptors. The contextual data is not sharable across separate
                target class method invocations or lifecycle callback events.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="bb">
            <text>If interceptors are invoked as a result of the invocation on a web service endpoint, the map returned by getContextData() will be the JAX-WS
                MessageContext.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>The getTarget method returns the associated target instance. For the |AroundConstruct| lifecycle callback interceptor method, |getTarget|
                returns |null| if called before the proceed method returns.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="da" testable="false">
            <text>The |getTimer| method returns the timer object associated with a timeout method invocation.</text>
            <note>Duplicate of 2.7 f)</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="db">
            <text>The |getTimer| method returns |null| for around-invoke methods and lifecycle callback interceptor methods.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="ea">
            <text>The |getMethod| method returns the method of the target class for which the interceptor was invoked.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="eb">
            <text>In a lifecycle callback interceptor for which there is no corresponding lifecycle callback method on the target class or in the
                |AroundConstruct| lifecycle callback interceptor method, getMethod returns |null|.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="f">
            <text>The |getParameters| method returns the parameters of the method or constructor invocation. If the |setParameters| method has been called,
                getParameters returns the values to which the parameters have been set.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>The |setParameters| method modifies the parameters used for the target class method or constructor invocation. Modifying the parameter values
                does not affect the determination of the method or the constructor that is invoked on the target class. The parameter types must match the types
                for the target class method or constructor, and the number of parameters supplied must equal the number of parameters on the target class method
                or constructor, or the |IllegalArgumentException| is thrown.
            </text>
            <assertion id="ga">
                <text>Test |setParameters| method modifies the parameters used.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="gb">
                <text>Test invalid number of parameters.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="gc">
                <text>Test invalid parameter types.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <group>
            <text>The |proceed| method causes the invocation of the next interceptor method in the chain, or, when called from the last around-invoke or
                around-timeout interceptor method, the target class method.
            </text>
            <assertion id="ha">
                <text>Test around-invoke interceptor method.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="hb">
                <text>Test around-timeout interceptor method.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="i">
            <text>For |AroundConstruct| lifecycle callback interceptor methods, the invocation of the last interceptor method in the chain causes the target
                instance to be created.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="j">
            <text>Interceptor methods must always call the |InvocationContext.proceed| method or no subsequent interceptor methods, target class method, or
                lifecycle callback methods will be invoked, or the target instance will not be created.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="k">
            <text>If a method is of type void, the invocation of the |proceed| method returns |null|.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="l">
            <text>For all other lifecycle callback interceptor methods, if there is no callback method defined on the target class, the invocation of proceed in
                the last interceptor method in the chain is a no-op, and null is returned.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="m" testable="false">
            <text>In case of the |PostConstruct| interceptor, if there is no callback method defined on the target class, the invocation of
                |InvocationContext.proceed| method in the last interceptor method in the chain validates the target instance.
            </text>
            <note>Unclear meaning of validation.</note>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="exceptions" title="Exceptions" level="2">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>Interceptor methods are allowed to throw runtime exceptions or any checked exceptions that the associated target method allows within its
                throws clause.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>Interceptor methods are allowed to catch and suppress exceptions and to recover by calling the |InvocationContext.proceed| method.</text>
            <assertion id="ba">
                <text>Interceptor method is allowed to catch and suppress exceptions.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="bb">
                <text>Interceptor method is allowed to recover by calling the |InvocationContext.proceed| method.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>The invocation of the |InvocationContext.proceed| method will throw the same exception as any thrown by the associated target method unless an
                interceptor further down the Java call stack has caught it and thrown a different exception.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="d" testable="false">
            <text>Exceptions and initialization and/or cleanup operations should typically be handled in try/catch/finally blocks around the proceed method.
            </text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="business_method_interceptor_methods" title="Business Method Interceptor Methods" level="2">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>Interceptor methods that interpose on business method invocations are denoted by the |AroundInvoke| annotation.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>Around-invoke methods may be defined on interceptor classes and/or the target class and/or superclasses of the target class or the interceptor
                classes. However, only one around-invoke method may be defined on a given class.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>Around-invoke methods can have |public|, |private|, |protected|, or |package| level access.</text>
            <assertion id="ca">
                <text>Test |public| level access.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="cb">
                <text>Test |private| level access.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="cc">
                <text>Test |protected| level access.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="cd">
                <text>Test |package| level access.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="d" testable="false">
            <text>An around-invoke method must not be declared as |abstract|, |final| or |static|.</text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-22</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="e">
            <text>An around-invoke method can invoke any component or resource that the method it is intercepting can invoke.</text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>In general, an around-invoke method invocation occurs within the same transaction and security context as the method on which it is
                interposing. However, note that the transaction context may be changed by transactional interceptors in the invocation chain.
            </text>
            <assertion id="fa">
                <text>Test transaction context.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="fb">
                <text>Test security context.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

    </section>

    <section id="int_methods_for_lifecycle_event_callbacks" title="Interceptor Methods for Lifecycle Event Callbacks" level="2">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>The |AroundConstruct| annotation denotes lifecycle callback interceptor methods that interpose on invocation of the target instance’s
                constructor.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>The |PostConstruct| annotation denotes lifecycle callback interceptor methods that are invoked after the target instance has been constructed
                and dependency injection on that instance has been completed, but before any business method or other event can be invoked on the target
                instance.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>The |PreDestroy| annotation denotes lifecycle callback interceptor methods that interpose on the target instance’s removal.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="d" testable="false">
            <text>The |AroundConstruct| interceptor methods may be only defined on interceptor classes and/or superclasses of interceptor classes. The
                |AroundConstruct| callback should not be defined on the target class.
            </text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-22</note>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>All other interceptor methods that interpose on the target instance lifecycle event callbacks can be defined on an interceptor class and/or
                directly on the target class.
            </text>
            <assertion id="ea">
                <text>Test |PostConstruct| interceptor method.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="eb">
                <text>Test |PreDestroy| interceptor method.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="f">
            <text>A single lifecycle callback interceptor method may be used to interpose on multiple callback events.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="g" testable="false">
            <text>Lifecycle callback interceptor methods are invoked in an unspecified security context.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="h">
            <text>Lifecycle callback interceptor methods are invoked in a transaction context determined by their target class and/or method.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="i">
            <text>|AroundConstruct| lifecycle callback interceptor methods may be defined on superclasses of interceptor classes. All other lifecycle callback
                interceptor methods may be defined on superclasses of the target class or of interceptor classes. However, a given class may not have more than
                one lifecycle callback interceptor method for the same lifecycle event. Any subset or combination of lifecycle callback annotations may
                otherwise be specified on a target class or interceptor class.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="ia">
            <text>If a lifecycle callback interceptor method returns a value, it is ignored by the container.</text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>Lifecycle callback interceptor methods can have |public|, |private|, |protected|, or |package| level access.</text>
            <assertion id="ja">
                <text>Test |public| level access.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="jb">
                <text>Test |private| level access.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="jc">
                <text>Test |protected| level access.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="jd">
                <text>Test |package| level access.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="k" testable="false">
            <text>A lifecycle callback interceptor method must not be declared as |abstract|, |final| or |static|.</text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-22</note>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="lic_exceptions" title="Exceptions" level="3">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>Lifecycle callback interceptor methods may throw runtime exceptions, but not checked exceptions.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>A lifecycle callback interceptor method (other than a method on the target class or its superclasses) may catch an exception thrown by another
                lifecycle callback interceptor method in the invocation chain, and clean up before returning.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>The |PreDestroy| callbacks are not invoked when the target instance and the interceptors are discarded as a result of such exceptions: the
                lifecycle callback interceptor methods in the chain should perform any necessary clean-up operations as the interceptor chain unwinds.
            </text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="timeout_method_int_methods" title="Timeout Method Interceptor Methods" level="2">
        <assertion id="a" testable="false">
            <text>Interceptor methods that interpose on timeout methods are denoted by the |AroundTimeout| annotation.</text>
            <note>Tested within the CDI TCK, 7.2 Container invocations and interception.</note>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>Around-timeout methods may be defined on interceptor classes and/or the target class and/or superclasses of the target class or interceptor
                classes. However, only one around-timeout method may be defined on a given class.
            </text>
            <assertion id="ba">
                <text>Test interceptor classes and/or superclasses.</text>
                <note>Partially tested within the CDI TCK, 7.2 Container invocations and interception.</note>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="bb">
                <text>Test target class and/or superclasses.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="c" testable="false">
            <text>Around-timeout methods can have |public|, |private|, |protected|, or |package| level access. An around-timeout method must not be declared as
                |abstract|, |final| or |static|.
            </text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-22</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="d">
            <text>An around-timeout method can invoke any component or resource that its corresponding timeout method can invoke.</text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>An around-timeout method invocation occurs within the same transaction and security context as the timeout method on which it is
                interposing.
            </text>
            <assertion id="ea">
                <text>Test transaction context.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="eb">
                <text>Test security context.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="f">
            <text>The |InvocationContext.getTimer| method allows an around-timeout method to retrieve the timer object associated with the timeout.</text>
        </assertion>
    </section>

    <section id="constructor_and_method_level_int" title="Constructor- and Method-level Interceptors" level="2">

        <assertion id="aa">
            <text>Method-level interceptors are interceptor classes associated with a specific business or timeout method of the target class.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="ab">
            <text>Constructor-level interceptors are interceptor classes associated with a constructor of the target class.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>Only the interceptor methods of the interceptor class that are relevant for the context in which the interceptor is bound are invoked. For
                example, if the interceptor is bound only to a business method, any |AroundConstruct|, |AroundTimeout|, |PostConstruct|, or |PreDestroy| methods
                on the interceptor are not called.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c" testable="false">
            <text>Method-level interceptors may not be associated with a lifecycle callback method of the target class.</text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-22</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="d">
            <text>The same interceptor may be applied to more than one business or timeout method of the target class.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="e">
            <text>The applicability of a method-level interceptor to more than one method of an associated target class does not affect the relationship between
                the interceptor instance and the target class - only a single instance of the interceptor class is created per target class instance.
            </text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="default_interceptors" title="Default Interceptors" level="2">
        <assertion id="a" testable="false">
            <text>Default interceptors are interceptors that apply to a set of target classes. If a deployment descriptor is supported, it may be used to define
                default interceptors and their relative ordering.
            </text>
            <note>Should be tested in the EJB TCK.</note>
        </assertion>
    </section>

    <section id="associating_int_using_int_bindings" title="Associating Interceptors with Classes and Methods using Interceptor Bindings" level="1">

        <assertion id="a" testable="false">
            <text>Interceptor bindings are intermediate annotations that may be used to associate interceptors with any component that is not itself an
                interceptor.
            </text>
            <note>Statement of intent</note>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="int_binding_types" title="Interceptor Binding Types" level="2">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>An interceptor binding type is a Java annotation defined as |Retention(RUNTIME)|. Typically an interceptor binding is defined as
                |Target({TYPE, METHOD, CONSTRUCTOR})| or any subset of valid target types.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>An interceptor binding type may be declared by specifying the |InterceptorBinding| meta-annotation.</text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="int_binding_types_with_additional_int_bindings" title="Interceptor binding types with additional interceptor bindings" level="3">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>An interceptor binding type may declare other interceptor bindings.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>Interceptor bindings are transitive - an interceptor binding declared by an interceptor binding type is inherited by all components and other
                interceptor binding types that declare that interceptor binding type.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c" testable="false">
            <text>An interceptor binding type can only be applied to an interceptor binding type defining a superset of it's target types. For example
                interceptor binding types declared |Target(TYPE)| may not be applied to interceptor binding types declared |Target({TYPE, METHOD})|.
            </text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-21</note>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="other_sources_of_int_bindings" title="Other sources of interceptor bindings" level="3">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>An extension specification may define other sources of interceptor bindings, such as via a CDI stereotype.</text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="declaring_interceptor_bindings_of_an_interceptor" title="Declaring Interceptor Bindings of an Interceptor" level="2">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>The interceptor bindings of an interceptor are specified by annotating the interceptor class with the binding types and the |Interceptor|
                annotation and are called the set of interceptor bindings for the interceptor.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>An interceptor class may declare multiple interceptor bindings.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>Multiple interceptors may declare the same interceptor bindings.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="d" testable="false">
            <text>An extension specification may define other ways of declaring an interceptor.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="e">
            <text>If an interceptor does not declare an |Interceptor| annotation, it could be bound to components using |Interceptors| annotation or a
                deployment descriptor file.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="f" testable="false">
            <text>All interceptors declared using the |Interceptor| annotation should specify at least one interceptor binding. If an interceptor declared using
                the |Interceptor| annotation does not declare any interceptor binding, non-portable behavior results.
            </text>
            <note>Non-portable mode</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="g" testable="false">
            <text>With the exception of |AroundConstruct| lifecycle callback interceptors, an interceptor for lifecycle callbacks may only declare interceptor
                binding types that are defined as |Target(TYPE)|.
            </text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-22</note>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="binding_int_to_component" title="Binding an Interceptor to a Component" level="2">

        <group>
            <text>An interceptor may be bound to a component by annotating the component class, a method, or constructor of the component class, with the
                interceptor binding type.
            </text>
            <assertion id="aa">
                <text>Test a component class.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="ab">
                <text>Test a method.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="ac">
                <text>Test a constructor.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <group>
            <text>A component class, method, or constructor of a component class may declare multiple interceptor bindings.</text>
            <assertion id="ba">
                <text>Test a component class.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="bb">
                <text>Test a method.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="bc">
                <text>Test a constructor.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>The set of interceptor bindings for a method or constructor are those declared at class level combined with those declared at method or
                constructor level.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>An interceptor binding declared on a method or constructor replaces an interceptor binding of the same type declared at class level or
                inherited from a superclass.
            </text>
            <assertion id="da">
                <text>Test a constructor.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="db">
                <text>Test a method.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <assertion id="e">
            <text>An extension specification may define additional rules for combining interceptor bindings, such as interceptors defined via a CDI
                stereotype.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="f" testable="false">
            <text>If the component class declares or inherits a class level interceptor binding, it must not be declared |final|, or have any non-|static|,
                non-|private|, |final| methods. If a component has a class-level interceptor binding and is declared |final| or has a non-|static|,
                non-|private|, |final| method, the container automatically detects the problem and treats it as a definition error.
            </text>
            <note>Tested within the CDI TCK, 9.3 Binding an interceptor to a bean.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="g" testable="false">
            <text>If a non-|static|, non-|private| method of a component class declares a method level interceptor binding, neither the method nor the component
                class may be declared |final|. If a non-|static|, non-|private|, |final| method of a component has a method level interceptor binding, the
                container automatically detects the problem and treats it as a definition error.
            </text>
            <note>Tested within the CDI TCK, 9.3 Binding an interceptor to a bean.</note>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="int_resolution" title="Interceptor Resolution" level="2">

        <assertion id="a" testable="false">
            <text>The process of matching interceptors to a certain lifecycle callback method, timeout method, business method or a constructor of a certain
                component is called interceptor resolution.
            </text>
            <note>Statement of intent</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>For a lifecycle callback, the interceptor bindings include the interceptor bindings declared or inherited by the component at the class level,
                including, recursively, interceptor bindings declared as meta-annotations of other interceptor bindings.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <group>
            <text>For a business method, timeout method, or constructor the interceptor bindings include the interceptor bindings declared or inherited by the
                component at the class level, including, recursively, interceptor bindings declared as meta-annotations of other interceptor bindings, together
                with all interceptor bindings declared on the constructor or method, including, recursively, interceptor bindings declared as meta-annotations
                of other interceptor bindings.
            </text>
            <assertion id="ca">
                <text>Test a business method.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="cb">
                <text>Test a timeout method.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="cc">
                <text>Test a constructor.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <group>
            <text>An interceptor is bound to a method or constructor if:</text>
            <assertion id="da">
                <text>The method or constructor has all the interceptor bindings of the interceptor. A method or constructor has an interceptor binding of an
                    interceptor if it has an interceptor binding with (a) the same type and (b) the same annotation member value for each member. An extension
                    specification may further refine this rule. For example the CDI specification adds the |jakarta.enterprise.util.Nonbinding| annotation,
                    causing member values to be ignored by the resolution process.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="db">
                <text>The interceptor intercepts the given kind of lifecycle callback or business method.</text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="dc">
                <text>The interceptor is enabled.</text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

    </section>

    <section id="int_with_multiple_bindings" title="Interceptors with multiple bindings" level="3">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>An interceptor class may specify multiple interceptor bindings.</text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="int_binding_types_with_members" title="Interceptor binding types with members" level="3">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>Interceptor binding types may have annotation members.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>Annotation member values are compared using the equals method.</text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>Array-valued or annotation-valued members of an interceptor binding type are not supported. An extension specification may add support for
                these member types. For example the CDI specification adds the |jakarta.enterprise.util.Nonbinding| annotation, allowing array-valued or
                annotation-valued members to be used on the annotation type, but ignored by the resolution process.
            </text>
            <note>Testing |jakarta.enterprise.util.Nonbinding| annotation.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="d">
            <text>If the set of interceptor bindings of a component class or interceptor, including bindings inherited from stereotypes and other interceptor
                bindings, has two instances of a certain interceptor binding type and the instances have different values of some annotation member, the
                container automatically detects the problem and treats it as a definition error.
            </text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="associating_int_using_interceptors_annotation" title="Associating Interceptors with Classes and Methods using the Interceptors Annotation"
             level="1">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>The |Interceptors| annotation can be used to denote interceptor classes and associate one or more interceptor classes with a target class,
                and/or one or more of its methods, and/or a constructor of the target class.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>Method-level around-invoke and around-timeout interceptors can be defined by applying the |Interceptors| annotation to the method for which
                the interceptors are to be invoked.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c">
            <text>Constructor-level interceptors can be defined by applying the |Interceptors| annotation to the constructor for which the interceptors are to
                be invoked.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="ca" testable="false">
            <text>Constructor- and method-level interceptors are invoked in addition to any default interceptors and interceptors defined for
                the target class (and its superclasses).
            </text>
            <note>Tested in section 5.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="d" testable="false">
            <text>If multiple interceptors are defined for the target class in the Interceptors annotation, they are invoked in the order in which they are
                specified. See Chapter 5 for the rules on interceptors ordering.
            </text>
            <note>Tested in section 5.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="e">
            <text>The Interceptor annotation is ignored on interceptor classes bound using the Interceptors
                annotation.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="f" testable="false">
            <text>
                An extension specification may support the use of a deployment descriptor to associate interceptor classes with a target class, and/or method or
                constructor of a target class, and to specify the order of interceptor invocation or override metadata specified by annotations.
            </text>
        </assertion>
    </section>

    <section id="int_ordering" title="Interceptor Ordering" level="1">
    </section>

    <section id="enabling_interceptors" title="Enabling Interceptors" level="2">

        <assertion id="a">
            <text>
                Interceptors declared using the |Interceptors| annotation are enabled by that annotation. Using the |Interceptors| annotation to associate
                interceptor classes with a target class or a method or constructor of a target class enables them for that target class, method, or constructor.
                The order in which the interceptor classes are specified in the |Interceptors| annotation controls interceptor ordering (see Section 5.2).
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b" testable="false">
            <text>An extension specification may define alternative mechanisms (e.g., a deployment descriptor such as the CDI beans.xml or the EJB ejb-jar.xml
                deployment descriptor) to enable and order interceptors, to override the order specified by means of annotations, or to disable interceptors.
            </text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

    <section id="int_ordering_rules" title="Interceptor Ordering Rules" level="2">
        <group>
            <text>Default interceptors are invoked first.</text>
            <assertion id="a" testable="false">
                <text>Default interceptors are invoked in the order defined by the extension specification (e.g., by their order in the deployment
                    descriptor).
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="b" testable="false">
                <text>If a default interceptor class has superclasses, interceptor methods declared in the interceptor class’s superclasses are invoked before
                    the interceptor method declared in the interceptor class itself, most general superclass first.
                </text>
            </assertion>
        </group>
        <group>
            <text>Interceptors declared by applying the Interceptors annotation at class-level to the target class are invoked next.</text>
            <assertion id="c">
                <text>Interceptor methods declared in the interceptor classes listed in the |Interceptors| annotation are invoked in the same order as the
                    specification of the interceptor classes in that annotation.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="d">
                <text>
                    If an interceptor class declared by applying the Interceptors annotation at class-level has superclasses, interceptor methods declared in
                    the interceptor class’s superclasses are invoked before the interceptor method declared in the interceptor class itself, most general
                    superclass first.
                </text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <group>
            <text>Interceptors declared by applying the Interceptors annotation at method- or constructor-level are invoked next.</text>
            <assertion id="e">
                <text>Interceptor methods declared in the interceptor classes listed in the Interceptors annotation are invoked in the same order as the
                    specification of the interceptor classes in that annotation.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="f">
                <text>
                    If an interceptor class declared by applying the |Interceptors| annotation at method- or constructor-level has superclasses, interceptor
                    methods declared in the interceptor class’s superclasses are invoked before the interceptor method declared in the interceptor class itself,
                    most general superclass first.
                </text>
            </assertion>
        </group>

        <group>
            <text>Interceptors declared using interceptor bindings are invoked next.</text>
            <assertion id="g">
                <text>
                    All interceptors specified using interceptor binding annotations visible on the target class (e.g., specified on the class or visible on the
                    class because they were declared with the Inherited annotation) are combined with all binding annotations on the target method and sorted by
                    the priorities specified by the |Priority| annotation; and then the interceptor methods are invoked in order of priority. The |Priority|
                    annotation is described in Section 5.2.1.
                </text>
            </assertion>
            <assertion id="h">
                <text>
                    If an interceptor class declared using interceptor bindings has superclasses, interceptor methods declared in the interceptor class’s
                    superclasses are invoked before the interceptor method declared in the interceptor class itself, most general superclass first.
                </text>
            </assertion>
        </group>
        <group>
            <text>Interceptor methods declared in the target class or in any superclass of the target class are invoked last.</text>
            <assertion id="i">
                <text>
                    If the target class has superclasses, interceptor methods declared in the target class’s superclasses are invoked before an interceptor
                    method declared in the target class itself, most general superclass first.
                </text>
            </assertion>
        </group>
        <assertion id="j">
            <text>
                If an interceptor method is overridden by another method (regardless whether that method is itself an interceptor method), it will not be
                invoked.
            </text>
        </assertion>
    </section>

    <section id="priority_annotation_in_ordering_int" title="Use of the Priority Annotation in Ordering Interceptors" level="3">
        <assertion testable="false">
            <text>
                The |Priority| annotation can be used to enable and order interceptors associated with components that use interceptor bindings. The required
                value element of the |Priority| annotation determines the ordering. Interceptors with smaller priority values are called first.
            </text>
            <note>Tested within the CDI TCK, section 9.4 Interceptor enablement and ordering.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b" testable="false">
            <text>If more than one interceptor has the same priority, the relative order of these interceptor is undefined.</text>
            <note>Undefined behaviour.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c" testable="false">
            <text>The |Priority| annotation is ignored on interceptors bound to a component using the |Interceptors| annotation.</text>
            <note>INTERCEPTORS_SPEC-23</note>
        </assertion>
    </section>

    <section id="excluding_interceptors" title="Excluding Interceptors" level="2">
        <assertion id="a" testable="false">
            <text>
                Interceptors may be excluded from execution by means of the |ExcludeClassInterceptors| annotation and the |ExcludeDefaultInterceptors|
                annotation.
            </text>
            <note>Tested separately in the following assertions</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="b">
            <text>
                The |ExcludeClassInterceptors| annotation can be used to exclude the invocation of the class-level interceptors defined by means of the
                |Interceptors| annotation.
            </text>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="c" testable="false">
            <text>
                The |ExcludeDefaultInterceptors| annotation can be used to exclude the invocation of default interceptors for a target class or—when applied to
                a target class constructor or method—to exclude the invocation of default interceptors for a particular constructor or method.
            </text>
            <note>Should be tested in the EJB TCK.</note>
        </assertion>

        <assertion id="d" testable="false">
            <text>
                An extension specification may define other means for excluding interceptors from execution, such as by means of a deployment descriptor.
            </text>
        </assertion>

    </section>

</specification>
